人人影视
YYeTs.com
《边桥谜案》前情提要
Previously on The Bridge...
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
我是杰克·多布斯
I'm Jack Dobbs.
你是来探视的吗
Uh, so, you here to see someone?
探视你哥哥
Your brother.
翻译：冰蓝  圈圈  胖兔纯  Isabelle  蓬蓬裙  爱卿遛小鸟
■
我是桑娅·克罗斯  丽莎的妹妹
I'm Sonya Cross, Lisa's sister.
翻译：foolyangyang  小肚腩  屯栗子  FIFISAY  Wdjmhs  潇湘月影
你到底在找什么
校对：wdjmhs     轴轴：阿包  kitty  安妮
我现在还不确定
我看到了就知道了
这边到底怎么回事
What's going on down here?
后期：8T     总监：wdjmhs
昨天  有人想要杀我
Yesterday someone tried to kill me.
我确定那是我们自己人
It was one of my own men.
你来美国做什么
What do you plan to do in the U.S.?
美国前往墨西哥华瑞兹市
请出示护照
工作
Work.
美国前往墨西哥华瑞兹市
请出示护照
祝你愉快
Have a nice day.
那是什么
What the hell is this?
女汉子出马了
There she goes.
帮帮我
Help me.
来吧
Come on.
我走了  哥们
I'm out of here, dude.
拜托
Please.
我需要帮助
I need help.
我好冷
I'm cold.
你的衣服哪去了
What happened to your clothes?
上面有人血
There was man blood on them.
也许我们该报警
Maybe we should call the police.
不不
Oh, no, no, no.
请不要
Please don't.
我没事
I'm fine.
你能帮我
You can help me.
好
Okay.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
凯尔
Kyle.
你知道恩典吗  凯尔
Have you known grace, Kyle?
恩典
Grace.
洞穿万物的圣光
The light that goes through everything.
我不知道
I don't know.
我的已经耗尽
I've used up all of mine.
也许对你来说还不算晚
Maybe it's not too late for you.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
帮我
Help me.
你得帮我
You have to help me.
好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
拜托
Please, please.
如果你帮我
If you help me,
我就让你摸我下面
I will let you touch me down there.
给
Here.
我不穿粉色
I don't wear pink.
如果我再回去  他们会醒来的
Come on, they'll wake up if I go back in there.
会倒霉的
It would be bad.
我从没穿过粉色
I've never worn pink.
那是给妓女还有想当公主的小女孩穿的
It's for whores and little girls who want to be princesses.
好吧
Okay...
找别的衣服  拜托了  凯尔
Something else. Please, Kyle.
给
Here.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
丹尼
Danny.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你没看到吗
Can you see it?
看到什么
See what?
圣光从他身上褪去
The light coming off him.
我们该走了
We should go now.
你该跟他道别
You should say good-bye to him.
好吧
Okay...
再见
Good-bye.
边桥谜案  第二季第二集
坐下
Sit.
乖狗狗
Good dog.
颈动脉被割开
Tore the carotid.
对
Yep.
看起来不像刀伤
Doesn't look like a knife wound.
反正效果不错
Did the job though, didn't it?
为什么不用刀子
Why not a knife?
应该随手抓起什么吧
Used what was handy, I suppose.
这么突然
So unplanned.
自卫吗
Self-defense.
可能吧  也可能不是
Maybe, maybe not.
为什么车没熄火
Why keep the car running?
估计是需要一段时间让他的血流干
Took a while for him to bleed out, I suppose.
而且  这种油电混合车  很难说
Plus, these electric jobs, you can't tell.
这整件事要是有一点符合常理就好了
Be nice if something about this whole thing made sense.
车里好像还坐了一个女人
I think there was a woman in the car.
昨天你请假了对不对
You took a personal day yesterday, didn't you?
对
Yeah.
为什么
What for?
我有32天假没用呢
I have 32 unused personal days.
去看多布斯了吗
Did you go see Dobbs?
没  我没去看他
Nope, I didn't see him.
多布斯的弟弟
Dobbs's brother?
对  我们一起吃午饭了
Yes, we had lunch.
为什么
What for?
我给了他一张照片
I gave him a picture.
我们  一起  聊天了  他人很好
We... just... talked. He's nice.
你们聊什么了
What'd you talk about?
丽莎
Lisa.
我们聊丽莎了
We talked about Lisa.
那个人的哥哥杀了你姐姐
That man's brother killed your sister.
这不能说明他是罪犯
That doesn't make him a criminal.
从统计学上来说  没理由假定他也是罪犯
Statistically speaking, there's no reason to assume that.
扯淡
Bullshit.
如果我是个男人你会这样跟我说话吗
Would you be talking to me like this if I was a man?
-不会  -这就对了
- No. - Right.
你说得对
You're right.
还是专心工作吧
So why don't we just work.
好吧
Okay.
好
早
Morning.
我是埃尔帕索警局的桑娅·克罗斯
Sonya Cross, El Paso PD.
是你做的吗
That your work?
我告诉他们我不干那种事
I told them I don't do that kind of thing.
我本想打电话报警...
I-I was gonna call you and...
让你做什么  先生
Make you do what, sir?
狗吗
The dog?
你们是为地下室里那东西来的吧
I-I assume you're here about what's in the basement.
对吗
Right?
他们一个月前来找我
They, uh, came in about a month ago.
不清楚是怎么知道我名字和电话的
Didn't-didn't say where they got my name or number.
就说有活让我干
Just said they had a job.
是两个人吗
There were two of them?
没错  一个男人  一个女人
Uh, yeah, the... uh... um, a man and a woman.
那个女人
And this woman, she was...
看起来有点古怪
she was kind of peculiar, you know?
知道他们名字吗
Get their names?
不知道  我没问
No, ma'am. I-I didn't ask.
我很抱歉  但我跟他们说得很明白
I'm-I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but i-I was very clear with them.
我不想接这份工作
I told them I did not want this job.
那个男人威胁说要砍掉我的双手
The partner, he said he was going to cut off my hands
杀光我全家人
and kill my entire family.
再加上  他们付的是现金
Plus, they-they paid cash.
就在这里面
Um, it's-it's... it's right in here.
路易莎
Luisa?
起床  我要走了
还早呢
再睡会吧
不行
我得去上班
不用付了  警探
那谢谢了
你还好吗
我没事
奇瓦瓦州警察局
他被吓坏了
你丢东西了还是怎么着
怎么
很牛是吗  混蛋
你觉得自己很牛是吗
是不是想毙了我  混蛋
给你
拿着  混蛋
赶紧拿着  混蛋
快啊
给你  拿去
这是怎么回事
你个没种的孬货
马可
Marco,
冷静点
那些血迹洗不掉的
我们约好了的  记得吗
我记得
那就好
Bueno.
我们待会见
那个标本师说子弹是从狗身上取出来的
Taxidermist said he took this bullet out of the dog.
那尸体呢
What about the body?
指纹估计都被虫子吃光了
Well, the beetles pretty well took care of the prints,
只能去查牙医记录
so we'll submit dental records.
好吧
Okay.
那就好吧
乔  有什么可以效劳的吗
Joe, what can I do for you?
那是我们的狗
That's our dog,
扬基
Yankee.
在警方通报的犯罪现场资料中
The dog was mentioned in a crime scene
我们注意到了这只狗
flyer your department circulated.
我们正指望你们能帮忙
Well, we were hoping for help identifying the
确定车里死者的身份
John Doe in the car.
我要看这件案子的详细档案
I'm gonna need to see the complete file,
所有材料
everything you got.
能告诉我为什么吗
You want to tell me why?
要看过档案才能确定
Won't know until i've seen the file.
他们是一男一女  就像我刚刚说的
It was a man and a woman and, like I said,
我之前从来没见过他们
I never saw either 'em before in my life.
是他吗
That him?
是的  女士  就是他
Oh, yes, yes, ma'am, that was him.
那个女人什么样
What about the woman?
她像是他的老板
Well, she was... she was like the boss.
拿着个特别大的账簿
She had this big ledger book,
四处走动  看到什么都要记下来
and she went around taking notes about everything.
她的着装挺搞笑的
And she dressed kind of funny.
像虔诚的教徒或阿米什人
Um, churchy, or Amishy.
车里没发现毒品
So, no dope in the car,
标本师那里也没有
no dope at the taxidermist.
难道缉毒局会对标本狗感兴趣吗
This is the DEA taking an interest in stuffed dogs?
我们现在感兴趣了
We are now.
你们在标本师那里发现的死者叫吉米·泰卡
The John Doe you found at the taxidermist is Jimmy Tecca.
是我们的人
One of ours.
我们的卧底探员
Undercover field agent.
那狗也是
The dog, too.
节哀顺变
Sorry for your loss.
但案子是我们发现的  就是我们的
However, we caught the case. It's ours.
不  现在不是了
No, not anymore.
他们说这尸体的事了吗
They say anything about the body?
他们不太高兴
Um, they weren't too happy
因为我说需要用槌打它
when I said I needed to beetle it.
他们想把人尸做成标本吗
They wanted it mounted?
对  要摆好姿势  可是尸体腐烂得太厉害
Posed, yes, ma'am, but it was too far gone.
布满蛆虫  还要放尸气  而且...
Maggots and off gassing, and...
更别说这事完全是犯法的
Not to mention the illegality of it all.
但问题是  他们把尸体放在了储存袋里
Uh, but the problem was, they had it in a storage unit.
这种温度下放置了两天  我也无能为力
Two days in this heat, there ain't nothing I can do.
缉毒局的人来了
The DEA's outside.
吃奶糖不
Caramel?
法国生产的
They're from France.
中间是海盐夹心
They got this sea salt in the middle.
这糖对牙齿不好  不过我特别喜欢吃
They're hell on the crowns, but I like 'em.
-我不吃糖  -为什么
- I don't do sugar. - Why not?
有害健康
It's poison.
好吧
Okay.
那个...
So, um...
不如这样  我们何不都坐下来
tell you what. Why don't we sit down,
有个执法人员的样子  都专业些
and I'll tell you what I got, you tell me what you got,
好好谈谈  互相交换下情报
and we act like law enforcement professionals?
真挺好吃的
That's good.
给  再来一块吧
Yeah, here. Have another one.
这是谁
Who's that?
首席调查员桑娅·克罗斯
Lead investigator Sonya Cross.
桑娅  这是缉毒局的乔·麦肯齐和皮特·里瓦斯
Sonya, this is Joe McKenzie and Pete Rivas from the DEA.
进来吧
Come on in.
把门带上
Close the door.
颈动脉多处刺伤
Multiple stab wounds to the carotid.
乘客逃离了现场
Passenger fled the scene.
你认识他吗
You know him?
尤凡尼·加尔萨
Yovani Garza.
他是福斯托·加尔文的保镖
He's an escort for Fausto Galvan.
车上没有毒品
There were no drugs in the car.
这我们已经谈过了  桑娅
We've been over that, Sonya.
有乘客特征描述吗
You get a description of the passenger?
女性  黑发
Uh, female, brunette.
标本师说她身上带着什么总账
Taxidermist said she has some sort of ledger with her;
认为她是管事的
thought that she was in charge.
有意思
Interesting.
想起什么来了吗
Does that ring a bell?
可能是女朋友
Could be a girlfriend.
我们会查的
We'll look into it.
那泰卡探员呢
What about Agent Tecca?
泰卡探员和扬基在华瑞兹帮我们
Agent Tecca and Yankee were responsible for
缴获超过三顿毒品
over three tons of seizures,
逮捕了无数罪犯
dozens of arrests in Juarez.
他们沉重打击了福斯托·加尔文的生意
They put a serious dent in Fausto Galvan's operation.
他什么时候失踪的
When did he go missing?
上个月
Last month.
疑犯要把泰卡探员制成标本
Our suspects wanted Agent Tecca mounted,
但腐烂太严重了
but the decomp was too bad.
这些人都变态的
These people are depraved.
希望你们不要提到剥制过程
We'd prefer you leave out mention of the taxidermy.
-这种事会给家属造成伤害的  -当然
- Something like that can hurt the family. - Absolutely.
我亲自训练的泰卡探员
I personally trained Agent Tecca.
我们一起打保龄球
We're on the same bowling team.
好吧  你们准备怎么划分职责
Okay, um, so how do you want to chop this up?
泰卡是我们的人  案子由我们负责
Since Tecca was ours, we'll take the lead on that.
好  那我们负责查加尔萨
Good, good. We'll take Garza.
副驾驶上的人呢  那个女的
What about the passenger-- the woman?
那个也由我们负责
Yeah, we'll want to be in on that, too.
做任何事之前  请先跟我们协调一下
Just don't make any moves without coordinating with us.
好
Good.
狗要给我
And I want the dog.
不好意思  狗是这案子的证物
Oh, I'm sorry, the dog is evidence in this case.
这狗是他妈的英雄
The dog is a goddamn hero;
我不会让它坐在证物室里积灰尘的
I'm not gonna have it sitting in some evidence room gathering dust.
-这不合规...  -可以
- That is against pro... - You got a deal.
给你带了一个三明治
Brought you a PBJ.
处理掉了吗
Are they gone?
是的
Yes.
安全吗
Is it safe?
是的
Yes.
我上了巴士  把东西丢下了
I got on the bus and ditched,
照你说的那样
just like you told me.
好孩子
Good boy.
那么
So...
你现在想摸我吗
Do you want to touch me now?
想
Y-Yes.
但...
But...
不能在这儿
not here.
会开车吗
Do you drive?
刚刚拿到学习驾照
Just have my learner's permit.
那就是会开
So you drive.
但必须有成人陪同
Only with an adult.
我就是个成年人
I am an adult.
-到吃药的时间了吗  -还没
- Time for your daily two? - Not yet.
你还好吗
How's that going?
三小时之后会好很多
Go a lot better three hours from now.
别那副表情
Don't give me that look.
下午好
Hola, buenos tardes.
头一个小时300比索
300 pesos for the first hour,
之后每小时180比索
180 pesos for each additional hour.
先付钱
Pay in advance.
还有  厕所没有纸了
And we out of towels.
不是的  我们是来找劳尔·昆塔纳的
他在这家酒吧工作
不认识
我们能进去找找看吗
随你
谢谢
走吧
Come on.
来两杯可乐
Can I get two Cokes?
不来点威士忌吗
Sure you don't want to throw some whiskey in there?
这是工作时间
We're working.
是啊  我都忘了
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
盯着别人看是很不礼貌的
You know, it's rude to stare.
根本停不下来
How can you not?
他如此高大  又如此美丽
He's six-foot-four and gorgeous.
我的本能被召唤出来了
I'm finding myself genuinely aroused.
你好  我们在找劳尔·昆塔纳
你认识他吗
谁
Who?
劳尔·昆塔纳
Raul Quintana.
这样说不行
You're not saying it right.
博尼托
Bonito.
劳尔·昆塔纳
Raul Quintana.
我的神啊
Ay, chihuahua.
你真的是太太太性感了
So you are... like, that was muy, muy, muy es caliente.
我们想问你几个问题  关于你的阿姨米莉
We want to ask you some questions about your aunt Millie.
你们怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
你房东告诉我们的
Your landlord.
该死
Shit.
谁派你们来的
Who sent you?
没人
Nobody.
我们是埃尔帕索时报的
We're with the El Paso Times.
我们只是想问几个问题
We just want to ask you some questions.
你阿姨死后一周
Yeah, look, uh, a week after your aunt died,
你和你的亲属便被驱逐出境了
you and your relatives were deported.
看  我是时报的记者丹尼尔·弗莱
What... uh, look, Daniel Frye. The Times.
但你们六个月前已经获准避难
Six months after getting asylum.
都是狗屎
This doesn't mean shit to me.
我怎么知道你们不是条子
How do I know you're not cops?
相信我  我可不是警察
Uh, trust me, I'm not a cop.
他们驱逐你的时候有说理由吗
Did they give you a reason when they deported you?
我不想回答
I'm not doing this.
别  请你别走
Whoa, whoa. No, no, please don't go.
你什么都可以跟我们说
Yeah, anything you can tell us, at all,
比如那六千万  比如你阿姨
about the 60 million bucks, and your aunt,
都可以说说
that'd be amazing.
我们只想知道你阿姨
We just want to know how your aunt
怎么和贩毒集团搞上的
got mixed up with the cartel.
贩毒集团
Cartel?
我没什么好说的
I'm not talking about this.
请你们离开这
I want you to leave now!
老兄  淡定
No, no, chillax, bro.
别紧张
Just relax...
天啊  丹尼尔
Oh, my God, Daniel...
你说对了
You were right.
过来看看
Come take a look.
和我一起钓鱼的海关署朋友一小时前给的
A fishing buddy at ICE got me this an hour ago.
汉克看过了吗
Hank seen this?
没有
Nope.
缉毒局也同时要了这段监控录像
The DEA requested the same footage, same time.
死者就是他
There's your dead guy.
停
Stop.
倒回去
Run it back.
这里
There.
你觉得她信教吗
Would you call that "Churchy"?
我觉得她特别虔诚
I'd call that downright devout.
打印出来
Print it.
全面通缉她
Put out an APB.
不让汉克看  不告诉缉毒局吗
Run it by Hank? Loop in the DEA?
他们去调取海关署录像也没告诉我们
They didn't inform us they pulled the ICE tapes.
发布通缉令
Put it out.
遵命
Yes, ma'am.
不是说好一个小时后见面的吗
没错  但现在不是更好吗
请给我来一杯威士忌苏打
Eh, un whiskey soda, por favor.
谢谢
Gracias.
今天发生什么事了
你是想在这里审问我吗
不是  就是聊聊天
这样啊
你不相信我
没事
你今天这招很妙
非常妙
你这发生了很多事
所有人都知道该注意谁
他们把你从墨西哥派来
让我们以为你真的关心华瑞兹
所以你就抓了几个警察
把他们扔进监狱关了一周
以为事情就解决了
没有什么真相
马可
只有不同版本的真相...
够了  别说废话了
你想知道什么
看
Mira.
雨果·马科斯
在索尔街信号灯下被枪杀
被杀两小时前  你和他有过争执
他呀
Si, him.
关于什么
你想知道的就是这个吗
这可以很大程度上帮助我了解这件事
他跟我说了一些不该说的事
比如
你知道有人说怎么你们警局吗
年轻女人来到警局求助
而她们却再也没有出来
你正在踏入一条非常危险的道路
你确定你要这么做
请告诉我那是一袋子满满的纯氧
Please tell me that's a bag full of Oxy.
我给你买的阿司匹林
I got you aspirin.
阿司匹林没用的
Aspirin's useless.
要是有人问起我的伤口
Hey, if anyone ever asks,
就说我是在飙车族酒吧为了保护你弄的
I did this defending your honor at a biker bar.
好吧  随你便
Yeah, whatever.
丹尼尔  你害我们把这事搞砸了
You really screwed us on this, daniel.
这不是我的错
It's not my fault.
是我
It's me.
别过来  喂  喂
No, hey, hey, hey, hey.
你干嘛
What are you doing...
对不起  亲爱的  我刚刚是不得已
Sorry, honey, I had to do that.
打疼了吗
Does it hurt?
一点点
Uh, just a little.
我不想被人看见我跟你说话
I didn't want to be seen talking to you.
我阿姨死后发生了很多稀奇诡异的事情
Weird shit has been happening since my aunt died.
有人在跟踪你吗
Is someone following you?
一直都有
All the time.
谁
Who?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么有人要跟踪你
Why would somebody want to be following you?
你要找的人叫楚奇托
The person you want to talk to is Chuchito.
他帮我阿姨筹了钱
He helped my aunt with the money.
怎么筹的
In what kind of way?
这你得问他
You have to ask him.
你们是朋友吗
Were you guys friends?
差不多吧
Something like that.
我  我很担心
I'm-I'm worried.
已经一周没见到他了
Haven't seen him in a week.
我不敢去他住处
I'm afraid to go by his place.
为什么
Why?
我说了啊  我被人盯上了
I'm telling you, i'm being watched.
好吧  放松
Okay, relax.
如果你们找到他  叫他给他亲爱的回个电
If you find him, can you tell him to call his bomboncito?
-我懂了  -不是
- Oh, I get it. - No.
他发生了些事情
Something happened to him.
拜托你们了
Now, please...
我得走了
I have to go.
你找我有事
You wanted something?
对  进来吧
Yep. Come on in.
把门关上
Close the door.
你没告诉我你让库珀调取了海关署的监控视频
You didn't tell me that you had Cooper pull that ICE video.
我们有图片
We got an image.
所以你就直接对这个女人下了全面通缉令
And you went ahead and put out an APB on this woman?
是的
Yes.
桑娅  你当时在场
You were here, Sonya.
你也听到我们对那些人的承诺了
You heard what we had agreed to with those guys.
我们在这些事情上应该提前跟他们打招呼
We owe them a heads-up on something like...
我们得在她回墨西哥之前找到她
We need to find her before she goes back to Mexico.
我们希望你按规矩办事
We need for you to follow protocol.
他们没和我们共享移民局的录像带
They didn't share the ICE tapes with us.
桑娅  这样很容易激怒他们
Sonya, something like this is liable to set them off.
他们可能不让我们插手
They could shut us out...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你因为杰克·多布斯而生我的气  对不对
You're mad at me because of Jack Dobbs, aren't you?
不  和那个没关系
Nope. This has nothing to do with that.
不  有关系
Yes, it does.
你想知道什么  汉克
What do you want to know, Hank?
我和他上床了
I had sex with him.
全境通告的事我很抱歉
And I'm sorry about the APB.
接受道歉
Apology accepted.
好的
Okay.
就这样吧
你记得我吗
You remember me?
记得
Yeah.
我不记得你和你哥哥那么亲密了
I don't remember you and your brother being that close.
我们不亲
We weren't.
很高兴见到你警探
Good to see you, Detective.
真希望我也能这么说
Wish I could say the same.
如果你不在我旁边抽烟就更好了
Prefer if you didn't smoke around me.
-你不抽烟  -以前抽  现在不抽了
- Not a smoker? - Was. Know better now.
你想要什么  还是今天不过是
You want something, or is this just some good old boy
老伙计们的日常会面
meet-and-greet routine?
想和你谈谈某人
Just want to talk to you about someone.
或许你应该和她谈谈
Maybe you should have this talk with her.
这不是我的份内事
It's not my place.
所以你来见我吗
So you came to see me?
桑娅在注意力方面有点问题
See, Sonya has a focus problem.
她太专注  这使得她
She gets too focused-- makes her
能成为好警察  但自己的生活却搞得一团糟
a great cop, but... personal life is not so good.
我想她自己可以处理
I think she can handle herself.
我担心的不是她
It's not her I'm worried about.
警察工作教给你的一件事
One thing this job teaches you
坏事发生不是偶然  它早已埋下伏笔
is that bad doesn't just happen, it's bred in.
现在  你或许是个
Now, you might be a fine member
社会好成员  为人类福祉做出贡献
of society, contributing to the betterment of mankind...
但是  他是你哥哥
but... he's your brother.
你们有着同样的血液
You share the same blood.
你也经历了那些可怕的事
You share all the same messed-up
那些事使得一个人
shit that went into making the
变成杀人不眨眼的凶手
kind of human that takes the life of another human.
它在你的血液里  杰克
That's in you, Jack.
我知道这话听上去很残忍  可这是事实
I know that sounds harsh, but it's the truth.
我们都知道在那个旅馆房间里发生了什么
We both know what happened in that hotel room.
你告诉她了吗
You tell her that?
做一件仁慈的事
Do the Christian thing,
给你哥哥送葬
see your brother into the ground,
然后回到你来的地方去吧
and then go back to where you came from.
谁
我啊  马可  我是路易斯
你想干什么
队长想见你
我们一直在找你  但找不到
什么事
你会知道的
金色漆
进来
Come in.
把门关上
Close the door.
里瓦斯  你喜欢食人怪还是巨人怪
Are you an ogre man or a troll man, Rivas?
我管它们叫幼稚娘娘腔
I like call of duty and pussy.
你下定决心了吗
You make up your mind?
那个叫福斯托·加尔文的混蛋
That shitbird Fausto Galvan
把咱们的人处死了
was gonna hang our friend on a wall.
所以咱们也该以牙还牙
So let's hang him on one instead.
她现在在埃尔帕索
She's in El Paso.
我用不用召集咱们的人
You want me to get some guys together?
不用  我想让当地警察追捕她
No. I want to let the local cops chase her,
让他们开道
let them break trail.
这事儿该我们牵头
We should be lead on this.
不行  我们这边刚把行动报告打上去
No. The second we file an action report on this,
华盛顿那边就会知道
DC hears about it,
然后中情局就会掺和进来
and we have the CIA all up in our shit.
那么我们要小心才是
So we're careful.
还要低调
And quiet.
我最不希望看到的就是
The last thing I want...
墨西哥政府
is the Mexican government
为了他们的"新墨西哥"公关活动而抓住他
snatching him for their "New Mexico" PR campaign.
无论哪种情形
Either scenario,
他都不会关在科罗拉多的监狱受苦
he's not getting ass-raped in a Colorado supermax.
鱼和熊掌我都要
I want the whole enchilada--
既要让福斯托·加尔文在美国被捕
Fausto Galvan arrested in the U.S.,
在美国定罪  还要把他关进我们的监狱里
convicted in the U.S., and locked up in one of our prisons.
懂我意思吗
Are you with me?
就在这上面
It's right up here.
你觉得我们能发现什么
Who do you think we're gonna find?
小华还是小花
Chuchito or Chuchita?
-四号门对吧  -对
- Four, yeah?  - Yeah.
我们撬门试试吧
Might as well try, right?
门开着呢
Ah, it's open.
有人吗
Hello?
楚奇托
Chuchito?
快进  快进
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
走  走  走
Go, go, go, go.
天哪
Oh, my God!
真臭啊
Stinks.
把这个捂脸上
Hey... throw this over your face, huh?
多谢
Thank you.
有人吗
Hello?
丹尼尔  丹尼尔  我们不能那么做
Daniel, Daniel, we shouldn't.
大不了被抓呗
It's only bad if we get caught, right?
雷伯恩国民银行
Rayburn National... Bank.
丹尼尔  天哪
Daniel! Oh...
丹尼尔
Daniel!
别打开
Don't open it.
别  别打开
Don't-don't open it.
太迟了
Too late.
队长不住在这里
是的  但他确实在里面
之前住在这里的男人失踪了
他是谁
尤凡尼·加尔萨
尸体在埃尔帕索被发现
福斯托·加尔文的打手
你那个白妞朋友负责这案子
好吧
我想帮帮她
你能帮上大忙
你要派我去查这个案子吗
不
No...
我请求你去
马可·鲁伊斯
别来无恙
这是怎么回事
你不是找我帮忙吗
给你儿子报仇的事
你想怎么样
尤凡尼在为我护送一件重要包裹
一个女人
我要你找到她
赶在美国人之前
如果我拒绝呢
加尔文先生  这个人优柔寡断
我相信马可会做出正确的选择
鉴于我们的事业当前面临的危险
我建议你采取更谨慎的措施
更适合做这件事的人很多
他们很乐意为自己的忠诚而获得表彰
我们是一诺千金之人
不是吗  马可
你的手指怎么了
What happened to your finger?
我在换浴缸
I'm replacing the bathtub.
陶瓷质量差
The tiles are bad.
你知道怎么换吗
You know how to do that?
不知道
No.
好吧
Mm, okay.
我能进去吗
Can I come in?
当然
Sure.
你要喝杯水吗
Would you like a glass of water?
好的  谢谢
Yeah, sure. Thank you.
那天的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about the other day.
你大老远跑过来道歉吗
You came all this way to apologize?
不是
Mm, no.
不全是
Not really.
你在办尤凡尼·加尔萨的案子吧
Yovani Garza case, you have it, right?
是的
Yes.
缉毒局也介入了
DEA is involved, too.
好吧
Okay.
那情况就不同了
That changes things.
他是我们的人
He's one of ours.
墨西哥籍
A Mexican national.
他是贩毒集团的
He's cartel.
是的
Yes.
罗伯斯队长派我过来办这个案子
Captain Robles sent me here to work the case.
跟你合作
With you.
他派你来监视我们这些美国佬吗
He's sending you to keep an eye on the Americans?
对  差不多这个意思
Yeah, something like that.
我很高兴这个人是你
Well, I'm glad it's you.
我也是
Me, too.
能看看你都有什么线索吗
Can I see what you have?
当然
Sure.
只有这些
That's all we got.
可不太专业啊
Not a professional job, you agree?
车里还有谁
Who else was in the car?
他和一个女人起了争执
He crossed with a woman.
长得有点奇怪
Kind of strange-looking.
是啊
Yes, she is.
你认得她吗
Do you recognize her?
不认识
No.
好吧
Okay.
我看看你都查到了什么
So show me everything you have.
你那个在公园见到我的朋友...
Your friend who saw me in the park...
你是说德克西吗
You mean Dex?
德克西  他住哪
Dex. Where does he live?
什么
What?
他很可爱
He's cute.
我想知道他住哪
I want to know where he lives.
凯勒街
On Keller.
是栋前面有篱笆的绿房子
It's the green house with a hoop in front.
地址呢
Address?
不知道
I don't know.
我说了  是绿房子
Like I said, it's green.
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
说
Yes.
你怎么纹了这么多纹身
Why do you have all those tattoos?
用来纪念我认识的恶魔
They are marks to remember the demons I've known.
好吧
Okay.
不是真的恶魔
Not real demons.
真酷
Cool.
那是什么味道
What's that smell?
一只浣熊
A raccoon.
爬进来死掉了
It crawled in here and died.
没关系
It's okay.
私密的分享就应该保密
What's shared in private should be kept private.
你说呢
Do you agree?
是啊
Yeah. I guess.
你跟女人上过床吗
Have you been with a woman before?
没有
No.
想摸摸吗
Would you like to touch?
这儿吗
Here?
对
Yes.
我什么都看不见
I-I can't see anything.
没关系
That's okay.
终将有光
The light will come.
照彻你身
It will pass through you.